A Guide to the Secretary of the Budget, General Administrative Records, 1918-1922;
Library of Virginia
Library of Virginia
Secretary of the Budget, General Administrative Papers, 1918-1922
Library of Virginia
24960
Secretary of the Budget
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
Accession 24960 was received by the library from the office of the Secretary of the Commonwealth. However, the accession contained materials from three offices: the Commission on Economy and Efficiency; the Secretary of the Budget; and the Secretary of the Commonwealth. This collection is one part of this accession.
Historical Information
The first state budget was prepared by the staff of Governor Westmoreland Davis in 1920. A member of the Governor's staff served in the capacity of the secretary of the budget, until and act passed by the General Assembly on March 20, 1922, designated the governor as the chief budget officer of the state and authorized him to appoint a deputy to be called the director of the budget. The state government reorganization act passed on April 18, 1927, established the Division of the Budget within the Department of Finance (which existed only on paper). The division remained a part of the governor's office until and act passed on March 19, 1975, transferred it to the secretary of administration and finance. An act passed on April 12, 1976, changed the name of the division to the Department of Planning and Budget. The same act assigned the department the responsibility for creating state planning districts, formerly a duty of the Division of State Planning and Community Affairs.
The primary function of the department is to plan, prepare, and assess the budget for state expenditures. The department also assembles and disseminates date on the social, economic, physical, and governmental characteristics of the state, especially as they relate to future governmental planning.
Scope and Content Information
This collection is comprised of the administrative papers of Colonel LeRoy Hodges, the governor's secretary of the budget from 1918 until 1922, when the position of director of budget was established. Included in the collection are correspondence and reports from state agencies and institutions, as well as some maps, charts, and organizational diagrams. The collection is arranged into four (4) series: Correspondence, 1921; Budget files, 1918-1922; Special reports, 1918-1922; and Monthly reports, 1922. A description of the individual series is found with the folder listing. The original organization of the collection was maintained as much as possible, resulting in the overlapping of dates of folders.
Of particular interest are the reports of state agencies and institutions that were written by the Governor's Board of Mechanical Survey and institutions outside of the Commonwealth of Virginia, including the Institute for Public Service of New York and the Detroit Bureau of Governmental Research (Series III). Additionally, there are maps of the state highway system, architectural drawings of what is now Virginia State University, and maps indicating the residences of the student body of the College of William and Mary (Series III, Oversize).
It is important to note that there is an extensive amount of material concerning the Virginia penal system. During this time, Colonel Hodges was also president of the Penitentiary Board. The materials found in folders relating to the Penitentiary or other agencies within the penal system may be correspondence created as president of the Penitentiary Board, and not as secretary of the budget.
Contents List
- Correspondence 1921 (Box 1 and 4)
  Arranged alphabetically by folder title. Contains routine correspondence from the office of the Secretary of the Budget. While folders throughout the collection contain correspondence with the office of the Secretary of the Budget, this series contains folders that were maintained separately by the office. The majority of the correspondence in this series is that of the statistician, J. H. Bradford, with various state agencies.
  alphabetical
  - Correspondence: J.H. Bradford, Statistician 1921 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence: J.H. Bradford, Statistician 1921 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence 1921 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Budget Files 1918-1922 (Box 1-2)
  Arranged alphabetically by folder title. Contains correspondence and reports from state agencies regarding the budget. Often there are multiple folders for individual agencies, with overlapping dates. The original order of the collection was maintained as closely as possible resulting in overlapping of the dates of contents for various agencies and institutions. Generally, agencies with multiple folders break with the beginning of correspondence regarding the next budget year, but there are exceptions.
  Alphabetical
  - Accountant, State 1918-1921 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Accountancy, State Board of 1918-1921 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Adjutant General of Virginia, Office of the 1918-1921 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Agricultural Experiment Station, Virginia 1918-1921 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Agriculture and Immigration, Department of 1918-1921 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Architects, Professional Engineers and Land Surveyors, State Board for the Examination and Certification of 1921 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Art Commission 1919-1921 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Attorney General, Office of the 1918-1921 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Auditing Committee (General Assembly) 1919 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Auditor of Public Accounts 1918-1921 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Auditor, Second (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Banking Division (State Corporation Commission) 1918-1921 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Bar, Board for Examination of Applicants for Admission to the 1918-1921 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Blue Ridge Sanatorium 1920-1921 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Budget, Governor's Advisory Board on 1919-1921 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Budget Transfers, 1920-1922 [biennium] 1921-1922 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Capitol Building: Water tank, estimates and report 1920-1921 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Catawba Sanatorium, Proceedings of the Special Meeting 1919 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Catawba Sanatorium, Proceedings of the Special Meeting 1919 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Central State Hospital 1918-1921 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Central State Hospital: Budget Statement 1921 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Chamber of Commerce, Board of Trade 1921 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Charities and Corrections, State Board of 1918-1922 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Code of Virginia, Commission to Revise the 1918 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - College of William and Mary 1918-1921 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Confederate Memorial Association 1921 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Confederate Women, Home for Needy 1918-1921 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Convict Lime Board 1918-1921 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Convict Lime Grinding Plant, Irvington 1919-1921 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Convict Lime Grinding Plant, Staunton 1919-1921 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Cooperative Education Association of Virginia 1919-1921 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Corporation Commission, State 1918-1921 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Dairy and Food Division (Department of Agriculture and Immigration) 1918-1921 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Dairymen's Association, State 1919-1921 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Davis Building - Bills Paid 1918 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Davis Building - Employees 1918 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Davis Building Fund 1918 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Davis Building - Miscellaneous [Corner of Governor and Franklin Sts.] 1917-1919 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Dental Examiners, State Board of 1918-1921 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Eastern State Hospital, General Correspondence 1918-1921 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Embalming, State Board of 1918-1921 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Expense Forms 1918 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Farm Survey, Governor's Board of 1919-1922 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Fee Commission 1919-1921 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Fisheries, Commission of 1918-1921 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Forester, State (State Geological Commission) 1918-1922 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Game and Inland Fisheries, Department of 1918-1921 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - General Assembly of Virginia 1922 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Geological Survey, State (State Geological Commission) 1918-1922 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Governor's Advisory Board of Criminal Mental Hygiene 1920-1922 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Grounds and Public Buildings, Superintendent of (Register of Land Office) 1919 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Hampton Normal and Agricultural Institute 1918-1921 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Harbor Commission for Norfolk, Portsmouth and Norfolk County 1918 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Health Commissioner (State Board of Health) 1918-1922 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Health, State Board of 1920-1922 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Highway, State Commission 1920-1921 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Highway Commissioner, State 1918-1921 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Home for the Incurables at Richmond 1919-1921 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Horticultural Society, State 1919-1921 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Hospitals, Commissioner of State 1918-1921 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - House of Delegates of Virginia (General Assembly) 1918 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Industrial Commission of Virginia 1918-1921 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Industrial Home School for Colored Girls 1918-1920 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Insurance, Bureau of (State Corporation Commission) 1918-1921 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Labor and Industrial Statistics, Bureau of 1919-1922 (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Laboratory, State Board of Health 1920-1921 (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Land Office 1920-1922 (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - Land Office 1918-1920 (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - Laurel Industrial School (Prison Association of Virginia) 1918-1920 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Legislative Reference Bureau 1918-1921 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Legislative Research, Governor's Board of 1919 (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - Legislative Research, Governor's Board of 1919-1921 (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - Library, State 1918-1922 (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - Markets, Division of (Dept. of Agriculture and Immigration) 1918-1921 (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - Mechanical Survey, Governor's Board of 1919-1920 (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - Mechanical Survey, Governor's Board of 1920-1922 (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - Medical College of Virginia 1918-1921 (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - Medical Education, Commission on 1920 (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - Medical Examiners, State Board of 1918-1921 (Box 1, Folder 62)
  - Memorial Hospital, Richmond, Va. 1918-1921 (Box 1, Folder 63)
  - Museum, State, of Mineral, Timber and History 1919-1921 (Box 1, Folder 64)
  - Normal School Board, Correspondence 1918-1919 (Box 1, Folder 65)
  - Normal School Board 1920-1921 (Box 1, Folder 66)
  - Normal School for Women at East Radford 1918-1920 (Box 1, Folder 67)
  - Normal School for Women at East Radford 1920-1922 (Box 1, Folder 68)
  - Normal School for Women at Farmville 1918-1920 (Box 1, Folder 69)
  - Normal School for Women at Farmville 1920-1922 (Box 1, Folder 70)
  - Normal School for Women at Fredericksburg 1919-1921 (Box 1, Folder 71)
  - Normal School for Women at Fredericksburg 1918-1919 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Normal School for Women at Harrisonburg 1918-1920 (Box 1, Folder 72)
  - Normal School for Women at Harrisonburg 1920-1922 (Box 1, Folder 73)
  - Nurses, State Board of Examiners of Graduate 1918-1921 (Box 1, Folder 74)
  - Optometry, Virginia State Board of Examiners in 1918-1921 (Box 1, Folder 75)
  - Orthopaedic Hospital (State Board of Health) 1919 (Box 1, Folder 76)
  - Penitentiary 1918-1920 (Box 1, Folder 77)
  - Penitentiary 1920 (Box 1, Folder 78)
  - Penitentiary 1920-1922 (Box 1, Folder 79)
  - Penitentiary - The Beacon 1922 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Penitentiary, Board of Directors of the 1920 (Box 1, Folder 80)
  - Penitentiary, Board of Directors of the 1920-1922 (Box 1, Folder 81)
  - Penitentiary Dental Service 1921 (Box 1, Folder 82)
  - Penitentary Farm, State 1918-1920 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Penitentiary Farm, State 1920-1922 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Penitentiary Guard 1921-1922 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Penitentiary, Industrial and Education Departments 1920-1922 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Penitentiary, Orders to Print Annual Reports 1918-1922 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Penitentiary Printing Shop 1920-1921 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Penitentiary Printing Shop 1921 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Penitentiary, Psychologis 1922 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Penitentiary Woodworking Shop 1921 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Penitentiary Woodworking Shop, Division Superintendent of Schools - Correspondence 1921 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Pharmacy, Board of 1918-1922 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Piedmont Sanatorium 1918-1920 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Piedmont Sanatorium 1920-1921 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Pilots, Board of Commissioners to Examine 1919-1921 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Printing, Superintendent of Public 1918-1921 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Probihibition, Commissioner of 1918-1921 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Purchasing Agent, State 1920-1921 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - R.E. Lee Camp Soldier's Home, Richmond, Va. 1917-1921 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Religious and Educational Work in State Institutions, Interdenominational Board for 1920-1922 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Road Construction, Governor's Advisory Board on 1919 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Secretary of the Commonwealth 1918-1921 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Secretary of the Commonwealth - Automobile License Division, Survey of 1921 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Senate of Virginia (General Assembly) 1918 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Sinking Fund, Commissioner of the 1919-1921 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Southwestern State Hospital 1918-1920 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Southwestern State Hospital 1919-1921 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Southwestern State Hospital 1919 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Southwestern State Hospital - Attendants 1918 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - State Board of Education 1918 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - State Colony for Epileptics and Feeble-minded 1920-1922 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - State Colony for Epileptics and Feeble-minded 1918-1920 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - State Colony for Epileptics and Feeble-minded - Attendants 1918 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - State Crop Pest Commission (State Entomologist) 1918-1919 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - State Crop Pest Commission (State Entomologist) 1920-1921 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - State Live Stock Sanitary Board (State Veterinarian) 1918-1921 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - State Tax Board 1918-1921 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Superintendent of Public Instruction (State Board of Education) 1918-1920 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Superintendent of Public Instruction 1920-1922 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Supreme Court of Appeals of Virginia 1918-1920 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Travelers' Aid Society of Virginia 1919-1922 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Treasurer, State 1918-1921 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Uniformity of Legislation in the United States, Board of Commissioners for the Promotion of 1918-1921 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - University of Virginia 1918-1920 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - University of Virginia 1920-1922 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Veterinary Examiners, State Board of 1918-1921 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Virginia Council of Defense 1918-1920 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Virginia Home and Industrial School for Girls 1918-1920 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Virginia Home and Industrial School for Girls 1920-1921 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Virginia Industrial School for Boys 1920-1921 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Virginia Industrial Schools for Colored Girls 1920-1921 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Virginia Manual Labor School (Negro Reformatory Association of Virginia) 1918-1919 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Virginia Manual Labor School 1919-1922 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Virginia Military Institute 1918-1920 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Virginia Military Institute 1920-1921 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Virginia Normal and Industrial Institute 1918-1920 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Virginia Normal and Industrial Institute 1920-1922 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Virginia Polytechnic Institute 1918-1920 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Virginia Polytechnic Institute 1920-1922 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Virginia Polytechnic Institute - Extension Division 1920-1921 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Virginia School for the Deaf and Blind 1918-1920 (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Virginia School for the Deaf and Blind 1920-1921 (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Virginia State Fair Association 1919-1921 (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Virginia School for Colored Deaf and Blind Children 1918-1919 (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Virginia State School for Colored Deaf and Blind Children 1919-1921 (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Virginia Truck Experiment Stateion 1918-1920 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Virginia War History Commission 1919-1921 (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - Vital Statistics, Bureau of (State Board of Health) 1918-1921 (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - Weights and Measures, Superintendent of (Register of the Land Office) 1919-1920 (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - Western State Hospital 1920-1922 (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - Western State Hospital - Attendants 1918 (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - Western State Hospital - General Correspondence 1918-1919 (Box 2, Folder 57)
- Special Reports 1918-1922 (Box 3, 6 and 7)
  Arranged alphabetically by folder title. Contains reports written by the Governor's Board of Mechanical Survey and institutions outside of the Commonwealth of Virginia, including the Institute for Public Service of New York and the Detroit Bureau of Governmental Research. Authorship of the reports is noted when known. This series also contains maps of the state highway system, architectural drawings of what is now Virginia State University (Virginia Normal and Industrial Institute), and maps indicating the residences of the student body of the College of William and Mary, which are found in box 7, oversize materials. Please note that this series is, in all likelihood, not complete as some reports were lent out from the office of the secretary of the budget and not returned. Notes to this effect were found during the processing of the collection.
  - Accounting Procedure, Budget Survey Recommendations for 1919 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Americanization Program Survey Report 1919 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Auditor of Public Accounts - Special Reports as to Financial Condition of State Institutions 1918-1920 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Bank Resources of Virginia Special Report 1919 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Banking Division (State Corporation Commission) Special Report 1919 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Capitol Building - Special Committee on Heating and Ventilating 1920 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Capitol Building - Special Report of Governor's Board of Mechanical Survey 1919 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Central State Hospital: Miscellaneous State Reports 1919-1921 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Central State Hospital: Report by LeRoy Hodges 1921 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Co-Education in Virginia State-Supported Institutions (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - College of William and Mary: Service Maps 1918 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - College of William and Mary: Service Maps 1918 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - College of William and Mary: Special Report, Governor's Board of Mechanical Survey 1919 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - College of William and Mary; Survey Reports 1919 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Convict Lime Grinding Plant: Preliminary Report on Limestone 1919 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Convict Lime Grinding Plant, Staunton: Survey Report to the Governor 1919 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Convict Road Force: Special Report on the State Board of Charities and Corrections 1919 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Convict Road Force, State: Survey Report 1919 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Detroit's Tentative Budget, 1921-1922 - Detroit Bureau of Governmental Research 1921 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Eastern State Hospital: Miscellaneous Reports 1918-1919 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Eastern State Hospital: Special Report, Governor's Board of Mechanical Survey 1920 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Education, State Board of: Special Report 1919 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Education, State Board of, Division Superintendent at Richmond: Survey Report 1919 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Forest Resources of Virginia: Special Report by R.C. Jones 1919 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Health, State Board of: Survey Report 1919 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Highway Commission, State: Miscellaneous Special Reports 1919 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Highway Commission, State: Miscellaneous Reports 1919 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Highways, State - Road Construction: Special Report, Governor's Advisory Board on Road Construction 1919 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Highways, State - Road Construction: Special Report, Governor's Advisory Board on Road Construction 1919 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Highway System, The State (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Hospitals for Insane and Epileptics, State: Survey Reports 1919 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Industrial Home School for Colored Girls: Survey Report 1919 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Insurance of State Property: Special Report 1919 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Laboratory - State Board of Health 1920 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Laurel Industrial School: Special Report on the Farm 1919 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Laurel Industrial School: Special Report, Governor's Board of Mechanical Survey 1919 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Laurel Industrial School: Survey Report 29 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Mechanical Survey, Governor's Board of: Summary of Report of State Institutions 1919 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Memorandum to Governor Westmoreland Davis re: Financing Road Construction - Detroit Bureau of Governmental Research 1919 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Mineral Resources of Virginia: Special Report of Dr. Thomas L. Watson 1919 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Natural Resources of Virginia: Special Report of J. C. Dickerman 1919 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Normal School for Women at East Radford, State: Special Report, Governor's Board of Mechanical Survey 1919-1920 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Normal School for Women at Farmville, State: Report by LeRoy Hodges 1919 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Normal School for Women at Farmville, State: Service Maps (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Normal School for Women at Farmville, State: Special Report, Governor's Board of Mechanical Survey 1921 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Normal School for Women at Fredericksburg, State: Special Report, Governor's Board of Mechanical Survey 1919 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Normal School for Women at Harrisonburg, State: Report by LeRoy Hodges 1921 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Normal School for Women at Harrisonburg, State: Special Report, Governor's Board of Mechanical Survey 1919 (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Office Building, Need for State: Special Report 1919 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Orange Camps - Investigation by Board of Charities and Corrections 1921-1922 (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - Orthopaedic Hospital at Richmond: Survey Report 1919 (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - Penal System, Virginia: Special Report of State Board of Charities and Corrections 1919 (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - Penitentiary: Special Report, Governor's Board of Mechanical Survey 1919-1921 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Penitentiary: Survey Report, John S. Rae 1919 (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - Penitentiary Farm, State: Special Report, State, Board of Mechanical Survey 1920-1921 (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - Penitentiary Farm, State: Special Reports on Farm 1918-1922 (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - Penitentiary Farm, State: Special Report, State Board of Charities and Corrections 1919 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Penitentiary Farm, State: Survey Report 1919 (Box 3, Folder 47)
  - Piedmont Sanatorium: Report by LeRoy Hodges 1920 (Box 3, Folder 48)
  - Piedmont Sanatorium: Special Report, Governor's Board of Mechanical Survey 1919 (Box 3, Folder 49)
  - Port and Harbor Facilities, Virginia: Survey Report, Institute for Public Service of New York 1919 (Box 3, Folder 50)
  - Prohibition, Commissioner of 1921 (Box 3, Folder 51)
  - Public Works, Report of Survey of 1919 (Box 3, Folder 52)
  - Report on the Budget Survey of the Office of the Secretary of the Commonwealth, Division of Banking, Bureau of Insurance, Department of Game and Inlet Fisheries, Industrial Commission - Detroit Bureau of Governmental Research 1921 (Box 3, Folder 53)
  - Report on the Cost Accounting System for the State Highway Commission - Detroit Bureau of Governmental Research 1919 (Box 3, Folder 54)